<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MonoBlog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MonoBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:19:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Die untrennbare Verbindung zwischen Kunstwerk und Künstler: Eine Analyse in fünf Dimensionen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/kunst-kuenstler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:19:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/kunst-kuenstler/</guid>
      <description>Einleitung Die Symbiose von Kunst und Künstler stellt ein tiefgründiges Paradigma dar, das weit über die bloße materielle Realität eines Kunstwerks hinausreicht. In dieser Analyse beabsichtige ich, die essenzielle Verbindung zwischen Kunstwerk und Künstler in fünf Facetten zu erkunden: Sozial- isation, historischer Kontext, räumlich-zeitliche Determinanten, kultureller Bezugsrahmen und die Transition des Werks im Laufe der Zeit. Durch eine Betrachtung dieser Dimensionen strebe ich danach, die Unauflöslichkeit dieser Verbindung zu veranschaulichen und ihre fundamentale Bedeutung für die Betrachtung und Interpretation von Kunst zu reflektieren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Artist as a Sieve: Filtering Inspiration and Crafting Originality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/artist-as-a-sieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:11:45 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/artist-as-a-sieve/</guid>
      <description>The art world constantly discusses the processes and techniques that artists use to create their works. One such metaphor is that of the artist as a sieve; the artist uses their unique perspective and experiences to sift through the world&amp;rsquo;s chaos, selecting what will inspire their art. Through this process, they create something new and present it to the audience, who will have their own interpretations and reactions. In this paper, we will explore the metaphor of the artist as a sieve, its implications, and its relation to the act of creating art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/hi/</guid>
      <description>Hi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/MonoBlog/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;test&#34;&gt;Test&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
